# YVONNE GRACE F. ARANDELA



€ 0946 726 7790 yvonnegracearandela@gmail.com



yvonnearandela.github.io

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Passionate, flexible and goal-oriented data scientist with an eagerness to expand current knowledge and experience new and unfamiliar things relevant for professional and personal growth. Looking forward to apply and improve the learnings and skills developed through research, competitions, and in a start-up company.

#### **EDUCATION**

## BS in Computer Science Major in Data Science, 2018-2022

University of Southeastern **Philippines** 

Honors: Magna Cum Laude

#### **CERTIFICATES**

# Huawei Seeds for the Future (Batch

Huawei Philippines Nov 2021

## **Huawei Certified ICT Associate** Certification

Routing & Switching Huawei Philippines Dec 06 2019

#### SKILLS

Programming Time management

Data Analysis Adaptability

Machine Learning Collaboration

Research Communication

Problem Solving Leadership

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### DATA SCIENCE INTERN

#### **Esco Lifesciences Group**

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

Annotated images of seashells for an Al project

#### DATA SCIENCE INTERN

# SegriTech, Tikkly Agro Solutions Private Limited Feb 2021 - Aug 2021

- Annotated and augmented image data
- Developed a fruit detection model that detects fruit and its quality
- Deployed the model into a web application that processes an image, video, and live webcam feed

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

2021-2022 IT Research Congress Presenter

2022 Women in Computing Presenter

2019-2020 Huawei ICT Competition Philippines (Network Team) Participant

2019 Android Masters Competition Finalist (Games Category) Finalist